<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Response xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Status>ok</Status>
  <Result>
    <Page>
      <PageID>3001877</PageID>
      <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
      <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageocr/3001877</PageUrl>
      <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001877</ThumbnailUrl>
      <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001877</FullSizeImageUrl>
      <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageocr/3001877</OcrUrl>
      <OcrText>
        CORRESPONDENCE. 183



        [We much regret that we are unable to complete Mr. Tuffen West's

        valuable Notes in the present issue. The remainder, with the

        "Selected Notes from Note-Books " having reference thereto, with

        the explanation of Plates XVI., XVII., and XVIIL, will be

        given in our next. — Editor?^



        Corrceponbcnce.



        \The Editor does ?iot hold himself responsible for the opitiions or

        statements of his co-respondents^



        Sir,—



        In the Journal of Microscopy, etc., for April, Mr. Wheatcroft

        draws special attention to the fact that in studying the plant-

        remains found in Egyptians tombs, Dr. Schweinforth has not

        been " able to detect any peculiarities in the living plants which

        are absent in those obtained from the tombs." Mr. Wheatcroft

        says these specimens were gathered at least four thousand years

        ago, and he thinks it " would be difficult to produce better

        evidence of permanency of type." Precisely this argument was

        used with reference to the theory of permanency of type in

        animals. We v/ere told that the domestic cat, whether in the

        mummical state or in its pictured representations, was just the

        same in that remote Egyptian age as it is at the present day.

        But we know now that instead of finding permanency of type as

        the prevailing law amongst animals, we find species and orders

        fading into one another like dissolving views as we penetrate

        further back into the abyss of time. The changes are very

        gradual ; to lose a tooth would be far too sudden a transition.

        One cusp disappears, and then another ; then the tooth appears

        later, grows smaller, decays early, and finally disappears altogether.

        The same gradual changes occur in the modifications of the whole

        skeleton, but most noticeably in the limbs. The cat, so " exactly

        like " our cat of the present day, changes by almost imperceptible

        degrees into an animal which is neither cat nor weasel, but the

        progenitor of both ; the dog into an animal which is neither bear

        nor dog, but which has some characteristics of the two modern

        species.



        It is difficult to imagine how any paleontologist of the present

        day could expect that an animal would be likely to change

        perceptibly in such a brief second of geological time as four

        thousand years. The whole of the Tertiary period can only be
      </OcrText>
      <PageTypes>
        <PageType>
          <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
        </PageType>
      </PageTypes>
      <PageNumbers>
        <PageNumber>
          <Number>Page 183</Number>
        </PageNumber>
      </PageNumbers>
    </Page>
    <Page>
      <PageID>3001878</PageID>
      <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
      <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageocr/3001878</PageUrl>
      <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001878</ThumbnailUrl>
      <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001878</FullSizeImageUrl>
      <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageocr/3001878</OcrUrl>
      <OcrText>
        184 CORRESPONDENCE.



        expressed as a fraction when compared with the vast ages which

        must have elapsed wliilst the paleozoic and the mesozoic rocks

        were laid down ; and the post-tertiary, when man (as we know

        him) and the modern species of animals took their rise, is a mere

        insignificant sediment compared even to the tertiary period.

        How, then, shall we express the geological_insignificance of the

        human historical period ?



        Under domestication, it is true that the progress of evolution

        is more rapid than under normal circumstances. Yet man, so far

        as I am aware, has only succeeded in accelerating the evolution of

        one new family, that of the domestic dog, which can be traced

        through distinct lines of descent from the wolf and jackal. But

        the domestic dog becomes a true dog long before the oldest

        Egyptian mummy received its wrappings ; ^the cat, a far more

        modern and highly specialized carnivore, has not had time to

        change since it was first domesticated.



        What has all this to do with plants ? may fairly be asked. I

        do not pretend to any acquaintance with paleobotany, but I

        cannot help thinking that the laws which govern one great branch

        of living beings govern also the other, and that as animals vary by

        slow degrees during the vast ages of geological time, so plants

        must also change. We see cultivated plants alter just as rapidly

        under the hand of man, as domesticated animals; we see the

        forest tree of warm regions become the creeping shrub of Arctic

        climes ; therefore, we know that vegetable forms vary with the

        action of their environment as do animals. There is also the

        same tendency to the late evolution of higher forms which we see

        in animals, and a tendency in some of the lower forms to dwindle

        away ; as witness the giant calamites of the coal forests^ as com-

        pared with the pigmy horsetails of the present day. The Equiseta

        are to the calamites much what the modern newt is as compared

        with the ancient labyrinthodont. My contention is not as to any

        point of paleobotany, of which I am certainly not qualified to

        judge, but only as to the utter insufificiency of the^time which has

        elapsed since Egypt was a civilised kingdom, to^ produce' new

        species of either animals or plants.



        Should anyone wish to see how almost imperceptibly, but how

        surely, Nature works in altering " types," I would refer him to

        some of the later lectures of Professor Cope, in his " Origin of

        the Fittest." A more popular account is given by Oscar Schmidt

        in "The Mammalia" International Scientific Series.



        Yours faithfully,



        Alice Bodington.



        Vancouver.
      </OcrText>
      <PageTypes>
        <PageType>
          <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
        </PageType>
      </PageTypes>
      <PageNumbers>
        <PageNumber>
          <Number>Page 184</Number>
        </PageNumber>
      </PageNumbers>
    </Page>
  </Result>
</Response>