<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Response xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Status>ok</Status>
  <Result>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>85</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Antarctic Exploration &amp; Discovery</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains rare books, journals and field diaries relating to the exploration and biodiversity of Antarctica.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>59</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Archives from the Boston Metropolitan Park Flora</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>In 1894 the Metropolitan Park Commission in Boston, Mass. commissioned Olmsted, Olmsted &amp; Eliot to survey the plants of newly acquired woodland reservations. This collection includes 8,000 pages of correspondence, published books, articles, and maps documenting the progress of the survey. To learn more about the collection please visit us &lt;a href="http://hwpi.harvard.edu/botlib_projects/book/archives-and-specimens-boston-metropolitan-park-flora"&gt;&lt;b&gt;online.&lt;b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>62</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Art of Science</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains the rare books featured in the Australian exhibition "The Art of Science: Remarkable Natural History illustrations from Museum Victoria".</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>82</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>BHL at 10</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Celebrate BHL's 10th anniversary by browsing notable contributions from its consortium members. From 2006 and its first 10 institutions to 2016 and its &lt;a href="http://biodivlib.wikispaces.com/BHL+Consortium#BHLparticipatingInstitutions"&gt;32 organizations&lt;/a&gt;, BHL partners have digitized and made freely available some of the most remarkable works from their collections. Sit back, relax, and browse some of BHL's best!</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>63</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>BHL Australia</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains the titles contributed by museum and herbarium libraries in Australia, as well as by Australia's Royal Societies and Field Naturalist Clubs.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>19</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>BHL China</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Content contributed by our global BHL partners with the Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences. See the &lt;a href="http://www.bhl-china.org/"&gt;Biodiversity Heritage Library China website&lt;/a&gt;.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>79</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>BHL Europe</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Books and volumes contributed from partners involved in the Biodiversity Heritage Library Europe project http://www.bhl-europe.eu/</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>67</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>BHL Singapore</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains items contributed by National Library Board Singapore and its partner institutions in Singapore.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>40</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Blog Features</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>All items featured in Book of the Week posts on the &lt;a href="http://blog.biodiversitylibrary.org"&gt;BHL Blog&lt;/a&gt;</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>41</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Bone Wars Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Collection of items authored or edited by Edward Drinker Cope and Othniel Charles Marsh.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>37</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Carl Linnaeus Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Select items authored by or about the Swedish botanist, physician, and zoologist.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>53</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Celebrating Alfred Russel Wallace</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Selected items featuring the work of Alfred Russel Wallace (1823-1913), British biologist, anthropologist, geographer, environmentalist, and human rights advocate. The man who, independently of Darwin, arrived to the same conclusion on natural selection. In 1858 he corresponded with Darwin about his theory, prompting Darwin to finally publish the famous work, On the Origin of Species, in 1859.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>4</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Charles Darwin's Library</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Books that were a part of Charles Darwin's personal collection.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>80</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Color Our Collections</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>A collection of books with plates suitable for coloring. Created as part of the #ColorOurCollections event.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>49</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Curious and Bizarre Creatures</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>What do deep sea monsters, mermaids, hydra, dinosaurs, and Shakespeare have in common? They're all in this collection featuring some of the strangest books BHL has to offer.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>69</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Early Women in Science</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection features works by important women scientists working prior to the middle of the twentieth century.  Some of these women are well-known, and others have been only minimally recognized, but all are important for their unique contributions to their respective scientific fields. &lt;br/&gt;Part of the &lt;a href="http://earlywomeninscience.biodiversityexhibition.com/"&gt;Early Women in Science exhibition&lt;/a&gt;</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>6</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Engelmann Herbarium</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Botanical literature generated during expansion into the American West.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>38</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Engelmann Papers, Missouri Botanical Garden</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>The personal papers of the botanist George Engelmann include almost 5,000 letters from about 550 leading and amateur scientists in the United States and Europe in the middle decades of the 19th century.  The collection also includes the various scientific notes and written works composed by Engelmann during his life as a medical doctor living in St. Louis, Missouri.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>24</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Ernst Mayr Library of the MCZ, Harvard University</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains all books contributed to BHL by the Ernst Mayr Library.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>84</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Expanding Access to Biodiversity Literature</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Expanding Access to Biodiversity Literature, which is funded generously by the Institute of Museum and Library Services (IMLS), will significantly increase online access to biodiversity material by positioning BHL as an on-ramp for biodiversity content providers that would like to contribute to the national digital library infrastructure through the Digital Public Library of America (DPLA).</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>21</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Extinct Species</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Dinosaurs, dodos, and more. Selected books highlighting extinct species of plants and animals.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>13</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Field Museum Library</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains all books contributed by the Field Museum Library.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>18</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Fieldiana: The Flora of Peru</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains those Fieldiana:Botany volumes which comprise the series Flora of Peru.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>31</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Floral Mania</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>These books contain some of the most beautiful and unusual illustrations of flowering plants in BHL.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>76</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Fossil Stories</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Rocks hold the key to the history of life on Earth. "Fossil Stories" explores the world of fossils, the history of paleontology, and the men, women, and publications that shaped our knowledge of life preserved in these rocks. This collection includes seminal works in the history of paleontology.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>52</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Harvard University Herbarium, Botany Libraries</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains all books contributed by the Harvard University Herbarium, Botany Libraries.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>71</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Latino Natural History</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>
        &lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;This collection features items related to naturalists from — or who are descendants of people from — Mexico, Cuba, Puerto Rico, and Central and South America, often referred to collectively as Latin America. These Latino/a naturalists have influenced the study of the world's flora and fauna, and in many cases provided the foundation for the study of science in their home countries. &lt;br/ &gt;Part of the &lt;a href="http://latinonaturalhistory.biodiversityexhibition.com"&gt;Latino Natural History exhibition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Esta colección presenta títulos relacionados a naturalistas que son de — o son descendientes de personas de — México, Cuba, Puerto Rico, Centroamérica, y Sudamérica, paises a los que frecuentemente  se refiere como Latinoamérica. Estos naturalistas latinos/as han influido el estudio de la fauna y flora del mundo, y en muchos casos crearon las bases del estudio de ciencias naturales en sus países. &lt;br/ &gt;Parte de la exhibición &lt;a href="http://latinonaturalhistory.biodiversityexhibition.com"&gt;Latino Natural History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
      </CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>57</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Library of Congress</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains all books contributed by the Library of Congress.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>5</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Missouri Botanical Garden's Materia Medica</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>A title scanned for Trio Foundation.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>7</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Missouri Botanical Garden's Orchid Folios</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Titles scanned for the Trio Foundation, 2011</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>1</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Missouri Botanical Garden's Rare Books Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>A volume scanned as part of MBG's Rare Books Website.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>64</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Monsters Are Real</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Many of history's most fearsome legendary monsters are based on real animals. The BHL Monsters Are Real campaign explores the stories, people, books, and animals that inspired such infamous beasts as Sea Serpents, the Kraken, Hydra, Mermaids, and Leviathans. This collection includes the books that fueled such monster myths, as well as those that highlight the real identity of these beasts.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>60</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Museum Victoria</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains all books contributed by Museum Victoria, Australia.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>51</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Natural History Museum Library, London</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription />
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>45</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>New York Botanical Garden</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Items contributed from the &lt;a href="http://www.nybg.org"&gt;New York Botanical Garden&lt;/a&gt;.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>43</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Notable Women in Natural History</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>A collection of selected works created by women who made direct contributions to the study of Botany and Zoology either by way of authoring or editing works on the subject or by providing critical illustrations to support the works authored by someone else. This collection is by no means comprehensive.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>58</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Once There Were Billions</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Once an amazing diversity of birds—some in breathtaking abundance—inhabited the vast forests and plains of North America. But starting around 1600, species began to disappear, as humans altered habitats, over-hunted, and introduced predators. This collection includes books related to the exhibition &lt;a href="http://library.si.edu/exhibition/once-there-were-billions"&gt;"Once There Were Billions"&lt;/a&gt; which focuses on the extinction of four bird species: the Passenger Pigeon (Ectopistes migratorius), Great Auk (Pinguinus impennis), Carolina Parakeet (Conuropsis carolinensis), and Heath Hen (Tympanuchus cupido cupido.)</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>72</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Perkins Agricultural Library</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>The &lt;a href="http://library.soton.ac.uk/perkins"&gt;Perkins Agricultural Library&lt;/a&gt; was presented to Southampton University Library in 1946 by Walter Frank Perkins, compiler of the bibliography, British and Irish Writers on Agriculture (1929). The Library contains over 2000 books and 40 periodicals published from the 17th century to the late 19th century. The books include practical farming texts on crops, animals, buildings and farm machinery as well as encyclopaedias and textbooks. The &lt;a href="http://viewer.soton.ac.uk/library/image/52136644/1/"&gt;published catalogue is available online&lt;/a&gt; and the collection can be &lt;a href="https://www-lib.soton.ac.uk/"&gt;searched from WebCat&lt;/a&gt; by selecting 'Perkins collection' in the 'location' field. This is a digitisation project in progress with texts being added weekly to the collection. Should you have particular interest in any texts in the catalogue that are currently not available, please &lt;a href="mailto:digitise@soton.ac.uk"&gt;let us know&lt;/a&gt; and we will attempt to prioritise their digitisation and availability.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>22</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Publicaciones en Español</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription />
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>27</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Rarest of the Rare</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>These unique gems of the Biodiversity Heritage Library collection represent some of the rarest natural history works to ever hit the digital world.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>50</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Savants of Napoleon’s Egyptian Campaign</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Contributions of the French scientists who took part in Napoleon's Egyptian Expedition. These materials represent works by the scientists associated with the campaign or are later works by said scientists not necessarily related to Egypt.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>56</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Seed &amp; Nursery Catalogs</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection includes works issued as seed and nursery catalogs, originally published for the purposes of documenting trends, products, and expert advice related to botany, horticulture, and commercial agriculture.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>39</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Shark Week Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>A collection of works about sharks to celebrate &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shark_Week"&gt;Shark Week&lt;/a&gt;.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>77</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Smithsonian Field Books collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection contains titles and items from the Smithsonian Field Book Project, an initiative to increase accessibility to field book content through cataloging, conservation, digitization, and online publication.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>32</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Theodore Roosevelt Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Selected works authored, co-authored or introduced by Theodore Roosevelt dealing with Natural History. Also available in iTunes U.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>83</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Top BHL Partner Content</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>This collection represents the top downloaded books from each of BHL's Members, Affiliates, and Partners as of BHL's 10th anniversary celebration in 2016.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>74</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Under the Sea: World Oceans Day</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>In honor of World Oceans Day on June 8, we’ve compiled a collection of publications that represent important milestones in the progress of marine bioscience research and ocean exploration.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>28</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>UNEP-WCMC Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>The collection of content provided by the &lt;a href="http://www.unep-wcmc.org/"&gt;United Nations Environment Programme, World Conservation Monitoring Centre&lt;/a&gt;.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>46</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>Whales: From Bone to Book Collection</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>Select items about the anatomy, ecology and evolution of whales authored by notable authors and Smithsonian scientists, part of the Smithsonian Libraries &lt;a href="http://library.si.edu/exhibition/bone-to-book"&gt;"Whales: From Bone to Book" exhibit&lt;a/&gt;.</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
    <Collection>
      <CollectionID>78</CollectionID>
      <CollectionName>White Whale</CollectionName>
      <CollectionDescription>A collection of works that include information about the sperm whale (Physeter macrocephalus).</CollectionDescription>
    </Collection>
  </Result>
</Response>