<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Response
    xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <Status>ok</Status>
    <Result>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001790</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001790</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001790</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001790</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001790</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>104 The microscope 

very well, and a double stain of eosin and hsematoxylin is 
 excellent. 

Dog. — Some sections should be made as soon as the cord has 
 been hardened in the Erlicki's fluid, before placing the cord in 
 alcohol; in order that they may be stained in osmic acid ; others I 
 find give good results if the sections be placed in o'5 per cent, 
 methyl green for 1 2 hours ; wash well in distilled water, then place 
 in borax carmine. This shows the axis cylinder and ganglion 
 cells red, whilst the neuroglia comes out violet, the remainder green. 
 Erlicki washes his sections for two hours in distilled water before 
 staining in ammonia carmine. 

Horse. — Get some short transverse sections and place for 
 forty-eight hours in Ranvier's alcohol. Then snip pieces out of 
 the anterior horn of grey matter, place in 2 per cent, solution 
 ot i)icro-carmine for twelve hours or so, then tease the 
 multipolar nerve-cells out with needles and mount in Farrant, in 
 a shallow cell. 

To harden Spinal Cord and Brain in Erlicki's Fluid.— 

It takes about ten days, but will do so in half the time if we care 
 to take the trouble to keep it at a temperature of about 40 deg. 
 C. or 104 deg. F. It must be fresh each time and filtered before 
 use. It must be changed daily or nearly so, and when the tissues 
 are hard enough the fluid is washed away with tap water and the 
 tissues finished in alcohol, commencing with 75 per cent. 

Spinal Cord (Overlach's Method).— Place small pieces of the 
 spinal cord of a child in a 1 or 2 per cent, solution of ammonium 
 bichromate until hard (fifteen to twenty days) in a cool place. 
 Make sections, and place in a solution of chloride of gold, i part, 
 and potassium in 10,000 parts of water, which has been acidu- 
 lated by the addition of a few drops of hydrochloric acid. Then 
 wash in one part of hydrochloric acid in 2,000 — 3,000 parts of 
 water; then transfer for 10 minutes to a mixture of one part of 
 hydrochloric acid in 1,000 parts of ordinary alcohol ; then succes- 
 sively in absolute alcohol, oil of cloves, and Canada balsam. 
 After three or four hours the nerve network is visible. 

Krause's Method.— Hang fresh cord in a cylinder full of 
 Mviller's fluid. Attach a small weight to the lower end to avoid 
 torsion. After twenty-four hours, change Miiller for i per cent, of 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 104</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001829</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001829</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001829</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001829</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001829</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>THE ROMANCE OF SEED-SOWING. 141 

In Bitter-cress {Cardamine hirstita), a very common weed 
 on dry, open banks, the pod, at the proper moment, when the 
 seeds are ripe, suddenly rolls its two side-walls outwards and 
 upwards, and the seeds, lightly attached to a central delicate 
 membrane, are scattered six or seven feet away from the 
 plant. Even a puff of wind is sufficient to effect this purpose. 
 Wallflower acts similarly, but with less force, as may be seen 
 in any garden. 

Among our wild Geraniums there are many interesting cases. 
 Herb Robert, which everyone knows, has five seed-vessels arrang- 
 ed around a central elongated column. Each vessel is prolonged 
 upwards into a thin rod, which is at first attached to the column, 
 but is slowly separated from it ; the flower, which after blossom- 
 ing turns downwards, now becomes erect, the rods become 
 highly elastic, and presently separate from the column with great 
 force, often scattering themselves and their attached vessels to 
 as great a distance as twenty feet. We may find scores of these 
 flowers in the woodlands, each of them with the erect central 
 column alone remaining, perfectly bare, and w^e must look for 
 some time to find the scattered seed-vessels far away. 

In another. Geranium dissectiim, or Jagged Crane's-bill, the 
 rods remain clinging to the column together with the five vessels, 
 the seeds only being thrown off. Curiously enough, the vessels 
 split open on the side turned towards the central column, and it 
 would almost seem as if this were useless, but the plant has its 
 fashion of overcoming this difficulty. Just before the vessel 
 splits, the rod curls outwards, placing the vessel horizontally, and 
 so at right angles to the column. The vessel gradually opens as 
 the rod curls still more upwards, a delicate fringe of hairs keeping 
 the seed safely meantime, until, when the rod has gone far enough 
 to place the vessel nearly upside down, the hairs give way, and 
 the seed is ejected. In this species, therefore, we should find the 
 column, not bare, but surrounded at its top by the five curled-up 
 rods, each carrying its empty vessel with the inner face split and 
 looking upwards. 

In Dog Violet ( Viola ca?iina), the capsule is raised on a 
 long stem, and at maturity opens by three valves, each holding a 
 row of four or five seeds. The walls of the open valves now 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 141</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001830</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001830</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001830</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001830</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001830</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>142 THE ROMANCE OF SEED-SOWING. 

become dr}', and contract, the two edges approaching each other. 
 This, after a time, forces the seeds out with a jerk, throwing 
 them eight or ten feet off. In Sweet Violet and Hairy Violet 
 ( V. odorata and hirsuta), the capsules are not so raised, the stem 
 being almost absent, and the leaves all springing from close to the 
 root. Here, we find that their capsules simply open as they he 
 on the ground, suffering the seeds to fall out among the grass 
 near by. Not being raised aloft, if the capsules shot their seeds, 
 the latter would probably strike against the surrounding grass and 
 fall back again, so the valves develope no contracting power, such 
 being useless, and they simply open quietly. Dog Violet has 
 found a better device for dispersion, and so in many generations 
 has gradually developed a tall stem, from the top of which its 
 elastic capsules can do their work with good effect. 

In Common Balsam, or 'Touch-me-not,' the pod dehisces 
 through its whole length, and at maturity, if we gently press the 
 centre between the thumb and finger, it swells up under our touch, 
 parts suddenly, and away go the seeds. I have stood at one end 
 of a room twelve feet long, and by pressure caused a pod to throw 
 its seeds with force against the opposite wall. Again, go and look 
 at some of our Vetches, or at Broom in seed-time, and you will 
 find the pods split in two, with each half rolled or twisted on 
 itself, and the seeds gone. The pods possess a layer of woody 
 tissue at an acute angle to their axis. When this contracts, the 
 pod is, therefore, not curled up along its length, but twisted, like 
 a screw. Gorse, and some others of the Pea Order, open 
 with a sudden crackling noise, and shoot out the seeds. On a hot 
 August day you may stand by a clump of Gorse bushes and hear 
 a series of tiny reports, as one by one the pods burst. 

Two singular instances are worth notice. The fruit of the 
 Sand-box tree {Hura crepitans) of America is about as large as 
 an orange, with a dozen or more deep furrows, which indicate 
 as many internal divisions into carpels. When ripe, and under a 
 hot sun, each separate carpel splits simultaneously, the whole 
 bursting with a loud explosion. From this fact, the plant has 
 earned the soubriquet of the ' Monkey's Dinner-bell ' ! 

Squirting Cucumber {Ecbaliuju elaterium) is one of the 
 Gourd Order, and when ripe is full to tension of a viscid fluid. A 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 142</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001877</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001877</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001877</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001877</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001877</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>CORRESPONDENCE. 183 

[We much regret that we are unable to complete Mr. Tuffen West's 
 valuable Notes in the present issue. The remainder, with the 
 "Selected Notes from Note-Books " having reference thereto, with 
 the explanation of Plates XVI., XVII., and XVIIL, will be 
 given in our next. — Editor?^ 

Corrceponbcnce. 

\The Editor does ?iot hold himself responsible for the opitiions or 
 statements of his co-respondents^ 

Sir,— 

In the Journal of Microscopy, etc., for April, Mr. Wheatcroft 
 draws special attention to the fact that in studying the plant- 
 remains found in Egyptians tombs, Dr. Schweinforth has not 
 been " able to detect any peculiarities in the living plants which 
 are absent in those obtained from the tombs." Mr. Wheatcroft 
 says these specimens were gathered at least four thousand years 
 ago, and he thinks it " would be difficult to produce better 
 evidence of permanency of type." Precisely this argument was 
 used with reference to the theory of permanency of type in 
 animals. We v/ere told that the domestic cat, whether in the 
 mummical state or in its pictured representations, was just the 
 same in that remote Egyptian age as it is at the present day. 
 But we know now that instead of finding permanency of type as 
 the prevailing law amongst animals, we find species and orders 
 fading into one another like dissolving views as we penetrate 
 further back into the abyss of time. The changes are very 
 gradual ; to lose a tooth would be far too sudden a transition. 
 One cusp disappears, and then another ; then the tooth appears 
 later, grows smaller, decays early, and finally disappears altogether. 
 The same gradual changes occur in the modifications of the whole 
 skeleton, but most noticeably in the limbs. The cat, so " exactly 
 like " our cat of the present day, changes by almost imperceptible 
 degrees into an animal which is neither cat nor weasel, but the 
 progenitor of both ; the dog into an animal which is neither bear 
 nor dog, but which has some characteristics of the two modern 
 species. 

It is difficult to imagine how any paleontologist of the present 
 day could expect that an animal would be likely to change 
 perceptibly in such a brief second of geological time as four 
 thousand years. The whole of the Tertiary period can only be 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 183</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001878</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001878</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001878</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001878</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001878</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>184 CORRESPONDENCE. 

expressed as a fraction when compared with the vast ages which 
 must have elapsed wliilst the paleozoic and the mesozoic rocks 
 were laid down ; and the post-tertiary, when man (as we know 
 him) and the modern species of animals took their rise, is a mere 
 insignificant sediment compared even to the tertiary period. 
 How, then, shall we express the geological_insignificance of the 
 human historical period ? 

Under domestication, it is true that the progress of evolution 
 is more rapid than under normal circumstances. Yet man, so far 
 as I am aware, has only succeeded in accelerating the evolution of 
 one new family, that of the domestic dog, which can be traced 
 through distinct lines of descent from the wolf and jackal. But 
 the domestic dog becomes a true dog long before the oldest 
 Egyptian mummy received its wrappings ; ^the cat, a far more 
 modern and highly specialized carnivore, has not had time to 
 change since it was first domesticated. 

What has all this to do with plants ? may fairly be asked. I 
 do not pretend to any acquaintance with paleobotany, but I 
 cannot help thinking that the laws which govern one great branch 
 of living beings govern also the other, and that as animals vary by 
 slow degrees during the vast ages of geological time, so plants 
 must also change. We see cultivated plants alter just as rapidly 
 under the hand of man, as domesticated animals; we see the 
 forest tree of warm regions become the creeping shrub of Arctic 
 climes ; therefore, we know that vegetable forms vary with the 
 action of their environment as do animals. There is also the 
 same tendency to the late evolution of higher forms which we see 
 in animals, and a tendency in some of the lower forms to dwindle 
 away ; as witness the giant calamites of the coal forests^ as com- 
 pared with the pigmy horsetails of the present day. The Equiseta 
 are to the calamites much what the modern newt is as compared 
 with the ancient labyrinthodont. My contention is not as to any 
 point of paleobotany, of which I am certainly not qualified to 
 judge, but only as to the utter insufificiency of the^time which has 
 elapsed since Egypt was a civilised kingdom, to^ produce' new 
 species of either animals or plants. 

Should anyone wish to see how almost imperceptibly, but how 
 surely, Nature works in altering " types," I would refer him to 
 some of the later lectures of Professor Cope, in his " Origin of 
 the Fittest." A more popular account is given by Oscar Schmidt 
 in "The Mammalia" International Scientific Series. 

Yours faithfully, 

Alice Bodington. 

Vancouver. 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 184</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001964</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001964</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001964</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001964</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001964</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>[260] 

Sclccteb IRotes from tbc Society's 
 1Rote*=Book0« 

Parasite of Flying Fox. — This insect being supplied with such 
 claws, two to each foot, scarcely needs the adventitious aid of 
 either of the quaint zones of processes, or the equally curious 
 appendage at apex of thorax. The animal belongs to the Chirop- 
 tera, of the family Fteropodiz, or Rousettes. The term " Fox " is 
 in allusion to the dog-like form of head. The rough outlines (PI. 
 XVIII., Fig. lo) gives some idea of the head. They are native of 
 the eastern hemisphere, and are the largest of the bats. The 
 Kalong of Java, Pteropiis edulis, measures no less than five feet in 
 extent of wing and nearly two in length. They are nocturnal in 
 their habits, and are vegetable feeders. T. Smith-Rowe, M.D. 

The Rousette. — In addition to Dr. Rowe's remarks, I have 
 added a rough sketch (PI. XVIII., Fig. ii) of the skull of the 
 Rousette. In the East Indies, the chase of Pteropi forms a fre-. 
 quent amusement of the colonists. The flight of these animals is 
 slow and steady, and capable of long continuance. Their ravages 
 among the delicate oriental fruits occasionally cause much annoy- 
 ance to the inhabitants of these islands. Bevan Lewis. 

EXPLANATION OF PLATES XVL, XVIL, XVIIL, &amp; XXIV. 

Plate XVI. 

Upper portion. 

Diatoms in situ. 
 Fig. 1. — Cocconeis scutellum. 

,, 2. — Synedra superba. 

,, 3. — Podosphsenia Ehrenbergii. 

,, 4. — Rhabdonema arcuatum. 

,, 5. — Grammatophora marina. 

s.v. (" side view " in the technical sense ; sometimes it would 
 be more expressive if called ' ' end view. ") 

f.v., front view ; it is in this view that the cingulum ("con- 
 necting membrane ") is seen, centre portion ; all x 200. 

Middle portion. 

Several hairs from leaf of Vibermun lantana (Mealy 
 Guelder-rose), x 100. 

Lower portion. 
 6. — Caprella linearis, &lt;^ , x 8. 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 260</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001986</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001986</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001986</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001986</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001986</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>274 

INDEX. 

Page 
 Dammar and Cement ... 45 

Debore's Method ... ... 253 

Deutzia Gracilis, Calyx of ... 49 

Deutzia, Hair on Petals of ... 1 14 

Development and Life-History of 

the Tadpole 33, 65, 147, 203 

Diatoms, Marine ... ... l8o 

Diatoms, The Nature of ... 32 

Dissections of Insects ... 53 

Dog, Spinal Cord of... ... 104 

Double Stain for Nervous System 253 
 Double Stain, Gibbe's ... 254 

Earth's Surface, Movement of ... 92 

Earthworm, To Harden .. 55 

Economic Entomology ... 217 
 EggofBot-Fly .. 49,51,52 

Electrical Cement ... ... 40 

Elk-Horn Fern, Hair from ... 259 

English Tingis ... ... iii 

Equisetaceffi, Life History of ... 74 
 Erlicki's Fluid for Hardening 

Spinal Cord ... ... 104 

Farrant's Gum and Glycerine, 
 Mounting in 

Fern, Hair from 

Fern, Oblique Section 

Ferns, Ramenta of ... 

Ferns, Scales of 

Fish, Palatial Tooth of 

Fishes, The Air Bladder of 

Fly from Greenhouse 

Fly, Wing of 

Flying Fox, Parasite of 

Fogs _ ... 

Foraminifera from Sea Soundings 

Forster, J. A., on Economic Ento- 
 mology 

French Cement 

French Polish 

Freezing Tissues 

Fumigation 

246 

259 

47 

114 

"S 
 III 

197 

50 

258 

257, 260 

... 212 

112 

217 
 41 

43 
 103 

154 

Ganglion Cells, Aniline Blue for 250 
 Ganglion Cells, Carriere's method 250 
 Ganglion Cells, Staining ... 249 

Gasteropoda, Method of Preparing 

the Radula of ... ... 89 

Gatehouse, J. \V., on the Develop- 
 ment and Life History of the 
 Tadpole 33, 65, 147, 203 

Gelatine Cement ... •••44 

Gibbe's Double Stain ... 254 

Page 
 Gifford, J. W., on Apochromatic 

Objectives ... ... 9 

Giftbrd, J. W., on Preparations 

for High Powers ... 152 

Glass or Earthenware, Cement for 45 
 Glow-worm, Phosphoresent Light of 73 
 Glue, Liquid ... ... 42 

Glue, Marine ... ... 41 

Glycerine and Litharge ... 43 

Glycerine Mounts, Cement for ... 41 
 Gold Chloride ... ... 249 

Gold-size ... •••39 

Good Black Varnish ... ... 32 

Gray, Dr. Asa, the late ... 106 

Greenhouse, Fly from ... 50 

Guaiacum Varnish ... ... 42 

Gum, extra adhesive... ... 40 

Gum water ... ... 45 

Hasmatopinus suis ... ... 182 

Hair from Elk-horn Fern ... 259 

Hairs on Petals of Deutzia ... 114 

Hairs on Viburnum Lantana ... 180 
 Half-an-Hour at the Microscope 
 with Mr. Tuffen West 

47, 180, 255 
 Hardening Tissues ... ... 102 

Hay-fever, the Pathology of Pollen 

in ... ... ... 173 

Head of Blow Fly ... ... 260 

Hessian Fly, The .. ... 12 

Hessian Fly and its Parasites ... 88 
 High Powers. Preparations for ... 152 
 Histology, Practical Notes on 102, 249 
 Hogg, Dr. Jabez, on Pseudo-Hel- 
 minths ... ... 240 

Hogg, Dr. Jabez, on Entozoa from 

Human Tooth ... ... 170 

Horse, Spinal Cord of ... 104 

House-fly, Wing of .... ... 258 

Ink ... ... ... 254 

Insect Dissections ... •••53 

Insect World, The ... ... 172 

Instantaneous Mounting in Farrant's 
 Medium ... ... 246 

Instinct of Birds ... •••73 

Jaw of Mole, Section of 
 Judson's Cambridge Blue 

112 

254 

Kitton's Cement ... ... 42 

Krause's Method of Preparing 

Spinal Cord ... ... 104 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 274</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
        <Page>
            <PageID>3001988</PageID>
            <ItemID>22004</ItemID>
            <PageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001988</PageUrl>
            <ThumbnailUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagethumb/3001988</ThumbnailUrl>
            <FullSizeImageUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pageimage/3001988</FullSizeImageUrl>
            <OcrUrl>https://www.biodiversitylibrary.org/pagetext/3001988</OcrUrl>
            <OcrText>276 

INDEX. 

Selected Notes from the Society's 

51^ 

Page 

Note-Books 

Shamrock 

Shamrock, Pollen of 

Sheep Tick 

Shellac ... 

Shellac and Aniline ... 

Slide Labels, Mucilage for 

Smith's New Cement 

Smut of Wheat, Oats, and Barley 

Spider, Spinnerets of 

Spinal Cord, Brain, etc., to exam- 
 ine ... 

Spinal Cord, Fibre of 

Spinal Cord of Dog ... 

Spinal Cord of Horse 

Spinal Cord, To Harden 

Spinnerets of Spider 

Spinnerets of Spider, To Mount 

Spiral Fibre in Rhubarb 

Spiral Vessels, To Mount 

Spirit and Iodine Mixture 

Sponge, a Piece of ... 

Staining ... 

Staining Medullated Nerve Fibre 

Staining Isolated Ganglion Cells 

Stigmas, To Prepare, to Show 
 Pollen Tubes 

Stomach of Bee 

Sugar Cane 

Sugar Cane Sections 

107 
 51 

49 
 258 

39 
 40 
 46 
 46 
 93 
 "3 

102, 249 
 249 
 104 
 104 
 104 
 113 
 51 
 116 

117 

254 

50 

251 

253 
 249 

55 
 49 
 52 

48 

Tadpole, Development and Life 
 History of 33, 65, 147, 

Tarantula at Home, The 
 Taylor, Miss B., on Fogs 
 Testacella 

Tingis Hystricellus ... 
 Tingis, English 

203 
 II 
 212 
 117 
 109 
 III 

Tissues, To Cut 

Tissues, Freezing 

Tissues, Hardening ... 

Tongue, Section of ... 

Tooth, Parasitic Entozoa from ... 

Trap-door Spiders and their Nests 

Tuffen West, Half-an-Hour at the 

Microscope with... 47, 180, 255 

Page 
 103 
 103 
 102 

"3 

170 

84 

Varnish, Brown ... •••43 

Varnish, Canada Balsam ... 43 

Varnish, Copal ... •••43 

Varnish, Good Black ... 42 

Varnish, Guaiacum ... ... 42 

Varnish, Matt ... ••■43 

Vegetation, The Influence of the 

Moon on ... . . 146 

Vereker, Hon. J. G. P., on 

Numerical Aperture .. 155 

Vereker, Hon- J. G. P., Presiden- 
 tial Address ... ... i 

Viburnum lantana, Hairs of ... 180 
 Villi and Beading on Scales of 

Lepidoptera ... ... 167 

Ward, Dr. R. H., On Mounting in 

Farrant's Medium 
 Weigert's Method for Nervous 

System 
 West, Mr. Tuffen, 

with 
 Wheatcroft, W. J 

History of Equisetacese 
 White, Hard Varnish 
 White Zinc 
 Wing of House-Fly ... 

246 

250, 251 
 Half-an-Hour 

47, 180, 255 
 On Life- 

• • 74 
 .. 44 

• 44 
 .. 258 

Xylol for Central Nervous System 105 

Zinc, White 

44 

Revtews. 

Adventures in African Travel, Stirring 61 

Algebra Made Easy 

Amateur Work 

Ambulance Lectures 

Among the Cannibals of New 

Guinea 
 Ants, Bees, Dragon-Flies, etc. ... 

264 

64, 271 

190 

189 
 59 

Arctic Stories ... ... 64 

Arithmetic, A Higher ... 191 

Arithmetic, Exercises in ... 125 

Arithmetic for Beginners ... 192 

Art of Preparing Vegetables for 

the Table ... ... 196 

Astronomy, Elementary Lessons in 195 

</OcrText>
            <PageTypes>
                <PageType>
                    <PageTypeName>Text</PageTypeName>
                </PageType>
            </PageTypes>
            <PageNumbers>
                <PageNumber>
                    <Number>Page 276</Number>
                </PageNumber>
            </PageNumbers>
        </Page>
    </Result>
</Response>